trysmartsample.com 2013-12-25

# SMART SAMPLE is the leading word-of-mouth marketing (WOM) company

SMART SAMPLE, we are strongly committed to protect the personal information that is submitted by visitors to us and would endeavor to protect it from unauthorized use.

This policy seeks to cover private information of the visitors provided to SMART SAMPLE online.

SMART SAMPLE reserves its right to correct any part of the said content at any time as and when required at its sole discretion.

_**Features of the Policy:-**_

  * The information collected on this site shall only be used to provide the visitor with the best possible services. The information should not be copied, modified, uploaded, downloaded, published or republished, transmitted or otherwise distributed for commercial purposes without prior and explicit permission from SMART SAMPLE. The information shall not be shared with external organization. The material provided on this website, with or without any modification, is prohibited without prior permission of SMART SAMPLE. Such act shall amount to violation of copyright and would be deemed an illegal act.
  * In the course of using this website or availing the products and services vide the online application forms and questionnaires, SMART SAMPLE and its Affiliates may become privy to the personal information of its customers, including information that is of a confidential nature.
  * SMART SAMPLE is strongly committed to protect the privacy of the visitor and working towards offering the visitor a safe, powerful and online experience and to protect the confidentiality of the visitor’s information and its transmission through the world wide web and it shall not be held liable for disclosure of the confidential information when in accordance with this Privacy Commitment or in terms of the agreements, if any, with the visitors.
  * To avail some of the services offered by SMART SAMPLE, the visitor need to sign up by giving simple details that personally identify the visitor. SMART SAMPLE needs this minimal information to operate the online services and encourage the visitor to update this information as and when there are any changes.
  * _Cookies :_ Like most Internet sites,SMART SAMPLE uses small bits of data called "cookies" to enhance the Internet user's experience on the Web. SMART SAMPLE will not use these cookies to personally identify the visitor in any way, and these cookies in no way damage the visitor’s system or files. SMART SAMPLE.
  * The “cookies” store information about the preferences and passwords of the visitor and allow to move to different pages of the Site without having to re-enter the password information of the visitor. Any information collected is stored in secure databases protected via a variety of access controls and is treated as confidential information by us SMART SAMPLE.
  * _Opt Out :_ If the visitor do not want the benefits of cookies, there is a simple procedure that allows the visitor to deny or accept this feature. In order to "opt out" of the benefits of cookies, the visitor may manually delete the cookies by following the instructions contained in the Help section of the browser.

  * _**Industry Efforts to Protect Consumer Privacy :**_ SMART SAMPLE is committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Accordingly,SMART SAMPLE strictly adhere to all industry guidelines, if the visitor have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement, please contact at  [help@trysmartsample.com](mailto:help@trysmartsample.com.%20) SMART SAMPLE recommends that the visitor may have periodically reviewed this Privacy Statement, as SMART SAMPLE may update it from time to time. SMART SAMPLE will protect personal information of the visitor against unauthorized use, dissemination or publication in the same manner in which we would protect our confidential information of like nature. However under certain conditions we may share this information.

  * _**Use and disclosure of Personal Information :**_ SMART SAMPLE may use the personal information to improve its services and to keep the visitor updated about our new products or other information that may be of their interest. SMART SAMPLE may share information in the course of normal business operations, such as providing services to the visitor have subscribed for. It may become necessary for SMART SAMPLE to disclose your personal information to its service provider, agents and contractors in the course of normal business operations for the above referred purpose. However these parties would be required to use the information obtained from SMART SAMPLE for such purposes exclusively. SMART SAMPLE will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to ensure that the confidentiality of your information is maintained by imposing strict confidentiality standards on all the third parties to whom it discloses such information.

  * SMART SAMPLE may be required to disclose your personal information to the statutory authorities in connection with any legal process that may be initiated by such authorities in accordance with applicable laws.

  * SMART SAMPLE may occasionally invite selected third parties to participate in offers they feel would be attractive to customers of SMART SAMPLE.

  * SMART SAMPLE may also share the information to provide the visitor with superior services and a range of offers. It may use this information to advice of products, services and other marketing materials, which SMART SAMPLE thinks, may be of interest to you. We may also invite visitors to this site to participate in market research and surveys and other similar activities. If one desires SMART SAMPLE to limit such sharing whereby one would not like to be informed of offers available one may contact us at help@trysmartsample.com. Otherwise, SMART SAMPLE will use the customer information to improve the visitor experience on the site and make subsequent offers to the visitor on products which may be of interest to him / her.

  * _**Order Information:**_ When the visitor orders from Smart Sample, Smart Sample collect the name, address, phone number, email address of the visitor and responses to specific questions regarding the item ordered. In addition, Smart Sample also stores the responses given by the visitor in any questionnaires or surveys offered by SMART SAMPLE.

  * SMART SAMPLE collects the information from the visitor is used by SMART SAMPLE in the following ways:

  * To confirm any order(s) placed by the visitor, confirm delivery of his order and/or to invite him to give feedback to SMART SAMPLE on the item(s) they have ordered.
  * To ensure newsletter of SMART SAMPLE provides the visitor and offers are most likely to be interested in.
  * To provide customer summary statistics to current and prospective partners.

  * _**Exclusions from Privacy Policy:**_ Other websites that may be accessed by the visitor via website may have different privacy policies and access to such web sites will not be subject to this privacy policy. SMART SAMPLE recommends that the visitor may read the privacy statement of each such website to find out how they protect your personal information.

  * _**Amendments:**_ Due to changes in legislation or enhancements to functionality and content on the website, SMART SAMPLE may make changes to privacy policy (without being obliged to do so) and would reflect those changes in this privacy policy statement. Hence the visitors are requested to go through the privacy policy statement on a regular basis.

  * _**Non Binding:**_ Please note that this privacy policy does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party, nor is it intended to do so.

  * _**Personal Information Removal:**_ If you wish to be removed completely from SMART SAMPLE database, email us at help@trysmartsample.com with your request.

  * _**Our Commitment:**_ Rest assured, if the visitor elects to be removed from our database, his information will not be used by SMART SAMPLE, or sold, rented or distributed to a third party from the date make his request. If he chooses to remain on the database of SMART SAMPLE , he will receive exclusive information on free offers, contests, promotions and more!

SMART SAMPLE respects privacy and uses the information they have about the visitors with integrity and full disclosure. If they ever feel this promise has been broken, they should inform the authorities of SMART SAMPLE . The visitors can contact the authorities of SMART SAMPLE for any additional query, they need to get clarified.

  * _**Prohibited Actions:**_ While using this Site, the visitor agree not to, by any means (including hacking, cracking or defacing any portion of the Site) indulge in illegal or unauthorized activities including the following:

• Restrict or inhibit any authorized user from using this Site

• Use the Site for unlawful purposes

• Harvest or collect information about Site users without their express consent

• "Frame" or "mirror" any part of the Site without our prior authorization

• Engage in spamming or flooding

• Transmit any software or other materials that contain any virus, time bomb, or other harmful or disruptive component

• Remove any copyright, trademark or other proprietary rights notices contained in the Site

• Use any device, application or process to retrieve, index, "data mine" or in any way reproduce or circumvent the navigational structure or presentation of the Site

• Permit or help anyone without access to the Site to use the Site through your username and password or otherwise

At SMART SAMPLE, we only do what’s right for the customer and will at all time strive to ensure his privacy.
